========ED=======
ごめんね）
春上さん　お友達よ
Haruue-san?
It's your friend.
お友達って　初春さんたちじゃないんですか
My friend?
You mean, it's not Uiharu-san and the others?
さあ　どうかしら
Oh? Who knows?
絆理ちゃん　嘘　絆理ちゃん
Banri-chan...
No way...
Banri-chan?
絆理ちゃん　本当に絆理ちゃんだ
Banri-chan... You really are Banri-chan...
そうだ　初春さんたちに連絡しなきゃ
That's right, I need to contact Uiharu-san and the others.
響き合う願いが今覚醒めてく
脑海中回响着的愿望现已苏醒
譲れない未来のために
为了绝不可相让的未来
巡り逢う運命を超えたその先に
只因在超越命运的前方
この想い輝くから
这份思念正闪耀着光芒
ここじゃない未来に
在那并非归属的未来
想い託してみては
寄存着这份思念
強さの本当の意味を
继续寻找着那
搜し続けてた
强大的真正意义
ありのままの痛みを
将各种痛苦
受け入れるその意味を
全部承受的意义
明日へ走り続ける君に知った
是奔向明天的你告诉了我
巡りゆく景色が今流れてく
那眼前的景色现已过去
手繰り寄せた世界の先
那紧牵着双手的世界的前方
降り注ぐシグナルを躰で感じて
身体已感觉到其中所倾注的信号
解き放つ今全てを
此刻解放所有一切
Just truthin my heart
いつだって迷わないよ
无论何时都不应迷茫
消せない想いがあるから
因为有着无法磨灭的思念
解き明かす真実から瞳を逸らさずに
直视那已经揭开的真相
I'll reach the next stage to realize all.
確かな絆信じて
请相信这份羁绊
じゃあ　行方不明だった十名の子供たちはMARの研究室に保護されたのね
So, the ten children that went missing are now in custody at the research facility of MAR?
はい
Yes...
So they were found.
見つかったんだ
良かったじゃん　初春
Isn't that good news, Uiharu?
はい
Yeah...
But I didn't expect Kiyama to have something to do with this case too.
けど　今回の事件にも　あの木山が関係していたなんてね
子供達が目覚めるなら　学園都市が壊滅してもいいなんて
She said it didn't matter if Academy City was destroyed, as long as the children wake up.
むちゃくちゃにもほどがありますわ
That's way too reckless.
So, Telestina-san will find a way to wake up Edasaki-san and the others, right?
それで　枝先さん達を起こす方法は
テレスティーナさんが見つけてくれるんですよね
Oh...
Yeah...
取り敢えずは　一件落着ですわね
The case is closed for now, right?
どうかなさいまして
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
なんでも
お姉様のことですから　どうせ木山春生の事を気になさっているのでしょう
It's you we're talking about, so you must be worrying about Kiyama Harumi.
彼女から子供たちを取り上げてしまって本当に良かったのだろうかとか とか
You must be wondering whether taking the
children away from her is the right thing to do.
That's not...
そんなこと
お姉様の判断は正しかった
Your judgment was correct.
I believe so.
黒子はそう思いますの
However...
ですが　大概になさいますよ　お姉様
Please refrain from doing things like that!
Don't sneak into suspicious places like that all by yourself!
一人で怪しい場所に乗り込むなんて
If anything were to happen to you...
お姉様にもしものことがあったら　黒子は　黒子は生きられない
Uiharu,
初春　なにぼうっとしてるのよ　初春
I would... I would...
Why are you spacing out, Uiharu?
Oh, it's nothing...
いえ
I'm sorry...
Go to Haruue-san's place already.
早く　春上さんの所へ行って上げなよ
Oh, okay...
はい　って　あの
Wait...
Haruue-san will be happy.
春上さんも喜ぶよ　ほら　急げ急げ
Now, hurry up!
Don't push me like that.
そんなに押さないでくださいよ
ほら　もっと早く走りましょう
Now you should be able to run faster.
もう　佐天さんってば
春上さん待ってるよ
Haruue-san's waiting for you.
Haruue-san's happy face, hmm...
春上さんの喜ぶ顔　か
Umm...
ええと　お菓子にゲーム漫画　後は　あ　着替え着替えっと
Snacks, games and manga...
What else...
Oh...
Clothes to change into...
Huh?
Just waiting isn't good enough.
待ってるだけじゃ　だめなの
I have to find them myself.
自分から探しに行かないと
Haruue-san...
春上さん　よかったね
Good for you.
I would do anything to save those children!
あの子達を救うためなら　私はなんだってする
Even if everyone in this city turned against me, I won't quit!
この町の全てを敵に回しても　やめるわけにはいかないんだ
I'm sorry, doctor. I can't do anything now.
すみません　先生　今は何も
Umm...
あの
君か
It's you.
I have a friend named Haruue-san.
私の友達に　春上さんって子がいるんです
まだ知り合って間もないんですけど
We only got to know each other lately, but she evidently was a childhood friend of Edasaki Banri-chan.
彼女枝先絆理ちゃんと幼馴染だったんです
Haruue-san is a Telepath, and every time the Poltergeist incident happened, she would hear Edasaki-san's voice.
＜telepath＞　　　＜poltergeist＞
春上さんは精神感応者で 乱雑開放事件が起こるたび
枝先さんの声が聞こえてて
だから犯人じゃないかって疑われたり
That's why she was accused of being the culprit.
But still she tried her best to listen to Edasaki-san's voice.
それでも一生懸命枝先さんの声を聞こうとして
けど　枝先さんが見つかったから　だから
But since Edasaki-san was found... That's why...
だから　春上さん　とても喜ぶと思います
That's why...
I'm sure Haruue-san will  be happy.
What are you trying to tell me?
何が言いたいんだ
I don't know.
分かりません　分からないんですけど
I don't know but...
It was just a bit more until the vaccine was complete.
もう少しでワクチンは完成するところだった
If only I were able to get hold of the First Sample,
後はファーストサンプルさえ手に入れば　そうすれば　あの子達の暴走を鎮め
Then I would've been able to stop them from going out of control when they woke up.
目覚めさせることが出来た
I would have stopped them from that fate...
目覚めさせることが
Kiyama-sensei, let's go to the MAR with that data.
木山先生　そのデータを持って　MARへ行きましょう
I'm sure it'll be useful.
きっと役に立ちますよ
Then let's go see Edasaki-san and the others.
それで 枝先さん達に合わせてもらいましょう
That's impossible...
そんな事
会いましょうよ　皆で　会いに行きましょう
Let's see them all.
Let's go see them.
君には敵わんな
You're absolutely right.
So you brought the research material for that?
まあ　それでわざわざ今までの研究資料を
So...
それで　あの　枝先さん達に会わせてもらいたいんですけど
We'd like to see Edasaki-san and the others.
Unfortunately, that's impossible.
残念だけど無理ね
子供達は移送することになったの
The children are to be moved out.
They are going to a facility with better equipment than here.
ここよりも設備の整った施設に行くのよ
Where would that be?
どこの施設ですか
I can't tell you that.
それを教えるわけには行かないわ
あの子達のことはこちらに任せて頂戴
Leave the children to us; we'll take care of them.
MARが責任を持って直して見せるわ
We'll take the responsibility for treating them.
あ　そうそう　春上さんも一緒だから
Oh, yes, Haruue-san is with them too.
Why?
え？　どうして
だって　ずっと探してた仲良しのお友達なんだもの
She's a good friend that one of them has been looking for.
一緒にいたいんじゃないかな
I'm sure they want to be together.
But...
でも
選んで
Choose.
あ　はい？
Huh?
Which color?
何色　選んだ色が出たら　春上さんでも子供達でも会わせてあげる
If the color you chose comes out, then I will let you see Haruue-san or the children.
Uh-Umm...
あの
Well then, if you can't choose, how about yellow?
仕方ないわねえ　じゃ　黄色にしとく
Here.
はい　あら　残念　　茶色
Oh, too bad. It's brown.
か　からかわないでください
D-Don't tease me!
Oh? But I'm serious.
あら　私は真面目よ
I'm really sorry.
あら　ごめんなさいね
テレスティーナさん
T-Telestina-san?
でも　どうせこんなデータ　役に立たないから
This data is useless, anyway.
そろそろお時間です　木原所長
It's about time, Director Kihara.
すぐ行く
I'll be there right away.
木原？
Kihara?
あら　知らなかった
Oh, you didn't know?
My middle name is Kihara.
あたしのミドルネーム　木原よ
テレスティーナ＝木原＝ライフライン
Telestina Kihara Lifeline.
き　貴様
You bitch!
Kiyama-sensei!
木山先生　大丈夫ですか
Are you all right, Kiyama-sensei?!
木山先生
私たち忙しいの　そろそろお引取りいただけるかしら
We're busy.
Can you leave right now?
Have some tea.
お茶どうぞ
You're in a good mood, Saten-san.
ご機嫌ね　佐天さん
＜plotergeist＞
だって　これで乱雑開放事件が一見落着したんですよ
Because the Poltergeist incident came to a close.
It means we can go out and play again.
また皆で遊びにいけるじゃないですか
That's right.
そうね　最近　貴方達ちょっと変だったけど
You girls have been acting strangely lately, but
that probably means everything is back to normal.
これで元通りって感じ
Right, Shirai-san?
ですよね　白井さん
I'm always the usual me.
私はずっといつも通りでしたわ
はい
Here.
Oh, right.
そうだ　春上さん　いつ頃退院するのか　初春に聞いてみよう
I'll ask Uiharu when Haruue-san can leave the hospital.
The best part of summer is still to come, so we better enjoy it.
これから夏本場だものね　楽しまなくちゃ
Agreed.
ですわね
Hello, Uiharu?
もしもし初春　いまどこ
Where are you now?
S-Sa...
佐天さん
Uiharu?
初春
Why...
佐天さん
What happened, Uiharu?
どうしたの初春　初春
Uiharu?
If you keep crying, I can't tell what's going on.
ちょっと　泣いてちゃ分からないでしょう　ね　初春ってば
Hey, Uiharu...
It's heavy...
＜plotergeist＞
よいしょっと　乱雑開放関連の資料集め終わりました
I've finished gathering information about the Poltergeist incidents.
Throw all that out.
それ全部捨ててくれ
＜plotergeist＞
今MARから連絡があって　乱雑開放の件はもういいって
We got a call from the MAR just now.
They said the Poltergeist case is over.
No way... I put in so much effort!
そんな　頑張ったのに　何でですか
Why?
Beats me.
知らん　終わったからとしか言わないんだよ
They're only telling us after it's all over.
Isn't that strange?
それって　可笑しくないですか
Telestina Kihara...
テレスティーナ＝木原　本当にそう言ったんですの
Did she really say that?
それで木山春生は
And what happened to Kiyama Harumi?
分かりません
I-I don't know...
Calm down, Uiharu.
落ち着いて初春　大丈夫だから　ね
It'll be all right, okay?
Found it!
あったわ　テレスティーナ＝木原＝ライフライン
Telestina Kihara Lifeline...
She's related to Kihara Gensei?
木原幻生の血縁　孫
She's his granddaughter?!
What?!
何ですって
I came across the data by the research staff in a paper by Kihara Gensei.
この間の木原幻生の論文から　当時の研究所の職員データにあたったの
Which means... Telestina was Gensei's research assistant too?
ということは　テレスティーナは幻生の研究助手もしていたと
That seems to be the case.
そう言うことになるわね　ちょっと待って
Wait a second.
何ですの　テレスティーナが能力体結晶事件の最初の被験者
What?
Telestina was the first test subject of the Ability Body Crystal?
How could that be...
なんてことを
Wait a second!
って　ちょっと待ってください
じゃ　木原幻生は自分の孫を実験体にしたって言うんですか
You're saying that Kihara Gensei used his own granddaughter as a test subject?!
その孫が木原の実験を手伝って
And that granddaughter helped with Kihara's research and...
＜child error＞
でもて　春上さんと置き去りの子達を
Haruue-san and the Child Error children were...
Hey, what's going on?
ってどいうことなんですか
How would I know!?
私に聞かれたって分からないわよ
What should I do?
どうしよ　私　私
I... I...
Don't cry, Uiharu.
泣かないの　初春
But... Haruue-san...
だって
だって　春上さん　枝先さん達も
Edasaki-san and the others too...
So...
だから
What should I do?
どうしよう　どうしたら　私
What can I do?
When are you going to stop crying?
いつまで　そうやって泣いているつもりですの
Shirai-san?
白井さん
There are other more important things that we should be doing.
他にもっとやるべきことがあるでしょう
いつになったら　风纪委员の初春に戻ってくれますの
When will you return to being Uiharu from Judgement?
Change place with me.
交代してください
Please...
お願い
The possible places where Haruue-san was transferred to...
春上さん達の移送先を可能性のある場所を
Huh?
あれ　御坂さんは
Where's Misaka-san?
Huh?
Onee-sama?
お姉様
What are
you seeing
with your eyes
right now?
A Certain Scientific Railgun
现在你眼中
能看见什么？
はい　どうぞ　これをお使えになって
Here.
Please use this.
My, thank you.
まあ　ありがとう
婚後さん　あれからずっと入院なさってるでしょう
Kongou-san has been hospitalized since that time.
そんなにお悪いのかしら　心配ですわね
Is she that sick?
It's upsetting, isn't it?
今度お見舞いに行きましょう
Let's go visit her next time.
そうですわね
You're right.
いいから　行きなさい
Just go on.
By the way.
ちなみに　今のに例の子供達が乗ってたんだけど
Those children are in the vehicles.
いいの　追いかけなくて
Don't you want to go after them?
騙したわね
You tricked us.
怒った
Are you upset?
一体何を企んでるの
What kind of conspiracy are you up to?
企むだなんて
Conspiracy?
Kihara Gensei's granddaughter,
木原幻生の孫娘　それでいって能力体結晶最初の被験者
who was also the first test subject of the Ability Body Crystal...
お爺さんの実験体にされるなんて
You were used as a test subject by your grandfather...
なのに　アンタは幻生の研究を手伝い　子供達を連れ去った
Yet you helped in Gensei's research and took the children away.
一体どういうつもりなの
What are your intentions?
よく調べたじゃねーか　御利口さん
You did your homework. What a good student you are!
けどなあ　どういうつもりと聞かれて答えってやつはいねいんだよ
But there's nobody foolish enough to answer that question.
馬鹿
Dumbass!
そんなに知りたきゃ力尽くで言わせてみろうや
If you really want me to tell you the answer, make me!
This sound... Capacity Down?
＜capacity down＞
このキャパシティダウン
Oh, you know about it?
あら　知ってるの
どうして　あんたが
Why do you have that thing?
Because I'm the one who built it!
だって　これを作ったのはあたしだからだよ
作った
You built it?
<Skill out>
武装無能力集団に試作品を流したら　たくさんデータが集まってな
After I leaked prototypes to Skill-Out, I got tons of data.
お陰で　かなり性能アップしたぜ
Thanks to them, I was able to increase its power.
ま　その分ちっとばかしでかくなりすぎたかな
Well, it's become a bit too big, though.
武装無能力集団でも使い方次第じゃ　役に立つのな
Even Skill-Out can be useful if you know how to use them!
Don't screw with me.
ふざけんじゃないわよ
武装無能力集団はモルモットじゃない
Skill-Out aren't lab rats!
Don't be mad.
怒っちゃ嫌
何だよ　調整が今一じゃないか
What? It isn't configured correctly?
でもまあ　それも面白いか
Well, that makes it more fun.
Why you...!
このー
I can't use my power...
力が
Hey, hey, your power isn't reaching me!
ほらほら　全然こっちに届いてないよ
Run! Run! Level-5 girl!
ほらほら　逃げろや　レベルる５のお譲ちゃんよ
What's all the commotion about?
一体何の騒ぎですの
This is...
これは　なにが　どうなってますの
What in the world is happening?
Huh?
あれって　御坂さん
That's...
Misaka-san?
貴方見たいな子って　本当に素敵
Girls like you are lovely.
正義感に溢れて　頑張り屋で
So righteous and hardworking.
Thanks to you and your  friends, I was able to find those children.
そういう貴方やお友達のお陰で
あの子供達を見つけることが出来たわ
As a reward, let me tell you the secret.
だから　ご褒美に教えたあげる
My purpose is to finish the Ability Body Crystal.
私の目的は能力体結晶を完成させる事
I won't let anyone get in my way.
誰にも邪魔はさせねえ
Hey, we got a interesting lab rat.
おい　面白いモルモットが手に入ったぞ　誰か運んとけ
Someone, carry her.
Hold it right there!
お待ちなさい　貴方方がお連れになっているその方を
Are you just going to take that girl away?
You should know full well that she is a friend of Kongou Mitsuko.
私婚後光子の友人と知っての狼藉ですの
各隊状況は
All units, what is the situation?
Yellow Marble here. Nothing unusual.
イエローマーべル　異常なし
Brown Marble here. Nothing unusual.
ブランマーベル　異常なし
各隊そのまま予定通りに
All units proceed as plann—
This is Blue Marble! Railgun got away!
こちらブルーマーベル　超電磁砲をお取り逃がしました
だと
What the fuck?
I'm terrible sorry!
申し訳ありません
今すぐよ捜索しります　必ず探し出し
We are searching the area.
We'll surely find he—
I don't give a shit.
もういい　てめいらその場で首でも吊ってろ
Go hang yourself there.
Onee-sama!
お姉様
Are you all right, Misaka-san?
大丈夫ですか　御坂さん
痛いところとかないですか
Are you hurt anywhere?
What was I...
私　一体
Well, it's all thanks to me.
まあ　全ては私のお陰なんですの
I see that you want very much to hear about how I saved my friend from danger?
いかにして私が友人の窮地を救ったのか そんなにお聞きになりたいんのですか
You leave me with no choice, do you?
あ　そう　仕方ありませんわね
そもそも私があの場所に居合わせたの
I happened to be at that place because...
I see, you saved me...
そう　婚後さんが
あの女
That woman...
Onee-sama, you mustn't move yet.
お姉様　急に動かれては
どいて　黒子　こんなところで　暢気に寝てる場合じゃない
Don't stop me, Kuroko.
This isn't the time to be sleeping.
早く　春上さん達を助けないと
I have to hurry and save Haruue-san and the others.
ですから　それは
Like I said...
私が勝手に研究所に忍び込んで　頭にきて
I snuck into the laboratory and lost my cool.
I handed over the children, whom we
worked so hard to find, to Telestina...
せっかく見つけた子供達をテレスティーナに
And then everyone...
それで皆を
I'm the one to be blamed for everything.
全ての責任は私にあるの　だから　私があの女を止める
That's why I have to stop that woman.
Step aside, Kuroko.
退きなさい　黒子
佐天さん
Saten-san?
Misaka-san.
御坂さん　今御坂さんの目には何が見えていますか
What are you looking at right now?
何って　佐天さん　だけど
What?
I'm looking at you, Saten-san.
私　ごめん　私なんか見えなくなってた
I...
I'm sorry...
I was being short-sighted.
また　皆に迷惑かけて
I brought trouble to everyone again.
It's not trouble to us.
迷惑なんかじゃないです
でも　離れて心配するくらいなら　一緒に苦労したいんです
But instead of worrying about you after you're gone,
I'd rather go with you and help you.
だって　それが友達じゃないですか
Because that's what friends are for.
Th-That's right!
そう　そうですよ　私達もいるんですから
We're here for you!
Right.
Yes...
ありがとう　皆
Thank you, everyone.
じゃ　次は初春　謝りなさい白井さんに
Okay, Uiharu's next.
Apologize to Shirai-san.
ずっと嫌な態度とって　ごめんなさいってしなさい
Say you are sorry for treating Shirai-san badly all this time.
ちょ　ちょっと　佐天さん
H-Hey, Saten-san...
You too, Shirai-san.
白井さんもです　初春ひっぱ叩いて　ごめんって　謝ってください
Eh?
Apologize to her for hitting her.
Huh...
I-I'm sorry, Shirai-san.
ごめんなさい　白井さん
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさいですの
So...
で　私には何かありませんの
Is there anything you want to say to me?
ありがとう　婚後さん
Thank you, Kongou-san...
I-It was nothing...
べ　別に構いませんけど
As I said, it's obvious that Telestina Kihara is involved in illegal activities!
ですから　テレスティーナ 木原が違法な行為をしているのは
もはや明らかなんですの
We already knew that her organziation was suspicious.
やつの組織が怪しいのは　こっちも分かってたんだよ
今いろいろ調べてから
We are conducting an investigation no—
There's no time for that!
そんな悠長に構えている時間はありませんの
Do something quickly!
どうにかしてくださいな
We can't act that easily.
そう簡単に動けねえんだよ
うちらにも限界ってもんがあるじゃん
We have our own limits, you know.
Didn't you say there is meaning in surpassing your limit?
限界を超えることに意味があるんじゃないんですか
You're... the girl from the courses...
お前　講習の時の
もう無理だったあきらめたら　そこで終わりだって言ってたじゃないですか
You said it's the end once you admit it's impossible.
このままじゃ　子供達が危険なんですよ
The children are in danger!
少し時間をくれ
Give me some time.
<Antiskill>
警備員から監視衛星のデータが来ました
Antiskill has sent us data from the surveillance satellites.
MARのトレーラは都市高速の５号線
The MAR trailers are on City Highway 5 and they just passed the 13th interchange in the 18th Academy District.
１８学区第三インターチェンジ通過したところです
５号線って　たしか１７学区につながってる道路よね
City Highway 5 is the road connecting to 17th Academy District, right?
１７学区　なんであんなところに
17th Academy District?
Why there of all places?
木原幻生が所有していた　施設の研究所があります
There's a private research laboratory that Kihara Gensei owned.
これ　このトレーラの後ろ走ってるのって　よれる
This...
Behind that trailer... Can you zoom in?
はい　木山先生
Yes.
Kiyama-sensei?
Geez. She went by herself.
たく　一人で行っちゃうなんて
背負い込んでじゃないわよ
Don't jump in on your own!
Onee-sama, I guess you're waiting for us to take a jab at you?
お姉様　それは突っ込み待ちということで宜しいんですの
Huh?
You two are quite alike.
案外似たもの同士なんじゃないですか
That's not true.
そんな事
And what am I supposed to do?
で　私は何をすれば宜しいの
You're still around?
まだ居たんですの
Here, drink this.
ほら　これ飲みなさい
腹が減っては戦はできぬ
We can't fight on empty stomachs.
しっかり食べなさい
Eat up!
はい
Huh?
あれ　この記録
These records...
狙い定めた指先が指す
Okay...
さて　行きますか
Let's move out.
A Certain Scientific Railgun
To be continued
運命は絶望 それとも希望
ゆらぎの中で受信してゆく
悲しみにも負けない
勇気だけをください
大切なもの　守るため
「強さ」があると信じてる
Saving our future 一緒に
明日へのドア開いた空へ飛び立とう
とある世界の果てで
駆け抜けてくReal Force
光を放って
Next Episode
Everyone let's go!
皆　行くわよ
テレスティーナを倒し　春上さんと木山先生
Let's beat Telestina.
Let's save Haruue-san, Kiyama-sensei and the children!
そして　子供達を助けに